# LAUTARO CONTE

Full Stack Developer

## CONTACT

#### **PHONE**

+54 11 6885 1595

#### **EMAIL**

info@contelautaro.com.ar

# **USEFUL** LINKS



GitHub



Linkedin



Web Portfolio

## **SKILLS**



**HTML** 



JavaScript





React



Node



TypeScript



Git



Design Patterns



Agile Methodologies

## **PROFILE**

I have been working in web development since 2019. I worked in projects as freelance Frontend Developer. Currently I'm taking courses about backend, all my work in progress is uploaded to my GitHub. Furthermore I have experience in social media, content marketing and SEO.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Full Stack Developer, Personal Web

Buenos Aires, Argentina

apr 2021— jun 2021

Personal web portfolio. JavaScript, GitHub Pages.

www.contelautaro.com.ar

### Full Stack Developer, Grupo Perri

Buenos Aires, Argentina

mar 2019 — Today

Web for insurance brokers. Docker, Wordpress.

www.grupoperri.com.ar

#### Full Stack Developer, Grupo Amado

Buenos Aires, Argentina

mar 2019 — jan 2021

Web for insurance brokers. Docker, Wordpress.

## **EDUCATION**

## Systems Engineering, UTN - Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

La Plata, Buenos Aires

mar 2019 — Today

## LANGUAGES

#### **English**

B2 First - Score 162